Come on, we're shining, running, forever!
The sea is calling out, so ride the waves!
We're all together as one,
so let's sail in the sun!
All our dreams are never ending, so
let's wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up!
Heartbeat, we will be one! Go ahead!
Even though our hearts have
traveled different paths.
We are best friends.
Our freedom is our only compass.
That's pointing us along the
many roads that come together.
We will keep on running forward every day.
Go east, go west.
As long as we keep looking to the horizon.
We'll see everything all crystal clear.
We're all so thrilled that we
can't wait until the dawn arrives.
So we'll just bring the
sun ourselves to know.
If the winds blow, it's waiting
where we should be going. Go.
That's right, we're
shining, running forever.
All of our dreams will
merge into one piece.
No matter where we go,
we'll be fine and free.
Cause all our treasure is our strength.
Come on, we're shining, running forever.
The sea is coming out, so ride
away, we're all together as well.
So let's just stay with the sun,
while our dreams are never-ending.
So let's wake up, wake up, wake up, wake
up, heartbeat, we will be one, go hey!
My darkness will swallow the
world, just you wait and see!
You think I'll lose to you?
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
Roger's treasure belongs to me!
We'll ride non-stop and travel farther.
than we've ever gone And then tomorrow
we will find suspense And then commence
to live out another day so intense
That's right, we're shining,
Running forever. Let's go along
with curiosity. Our feelings lead
the way straight to a brand new day Into
another adventure Come on, we're shining,
Running forever. Open the map inside your
heart and see. No matter where we end up,
Our mods will never give up. There's a
fire in our dreams and you can never,
never, never, never stop it
We will be one, go ahead!
Whoa, jeez.
Are they gonna toss
everyone down here or what?
It's grandpa!
Oh, inside too!
Oh, what smell?
Hello there! Boo!
So, is this some kind of trash heap?
Why are there toys everywhere?
What is this place, brother?
How am I supposed to know?
To think there was such a massive
junkyard hidden beneath the kingdom!
Them—excuse me!
I have a question!
I could be wrong if so,
forgive me, but you're him, aren't you?
Tell me please!
To think you've been alive
all this time, King Rick!
King Rick!
There's no way!
way You crazy.
The man's dead.
Did you hit your head
when you fell down here?
That old king lost his mind, didn't he?
Went on a rampage and had to be put
down like a wild dog, from what I heard.
We're far enough from
prying eyes, I suppose.
I might as well shed my disguise.
I couldn't hide the truth from you.
I am indeed Rick.
Though there is no need to call
me king anymore, Captain Tank.
It's really him.
He's been alive this whole time.
I'm so happy to see you, King Rick.
I can't even save my own granddaughter.
I'm just a sad old man
now, not worthy to be king.
It's been so long.
Forgive me, my lord.
With no flamingo in control...
Enough.
I trust you.
I know you've been watching
over Viola all this time.
I'm certain that you would not
abandon your duty or honor so easily.
I can only imagine how
much you've suffered.
No, it's nothing compared
to what you've gone through.
he's not kidding it really is King
Rick is that the king of Prudence none
other old friend so many times in the
past you've aided my kingdom oh I missed
you whoa there okay things haven't
been the same at all since you've been
away there's no stability between nations
these days. War all the time. I've
Had had enough. Had enough. Why don't
you wake up while you're crying? Someone
else is laughing all the way to the
bank ever think of that our nations
are being pushed into war with each
other all to suit someone else's agenda
it's a nice gig for a weapons dealer
the more we fight the richer they get
and in this case the one
to blame is a man known
as joker it's an alias
of doflamingo of course
as of yet we haven't determined where he
manufactures or stores his
weapons but we do know that
he's selling them to
our enemies locking our
kingdom into a war that
never seems to end we
entered this tournament
as an excuse to infiltrate
the city and search for
doflamingo's factory at
the bequest of the king
of kano we of the hapasui
army are working to
stem the tide of weapons
smuggling that plagues
this world king Rick
doflamingo's ascension to
the throne is the result
of you acting foolishly
and now all the nations
around you are suffering
what he says is true
king elizabello it is noble
of you to show gratitude
for the aidress Rosa
offered us in the past.
But those days are gone.
The name King Riku's been dragged
through the mud, and rightfully so.
Enough, Dagama!
We faced a nightmare ten years ago,
and the truth you know is a lie!
So shut your mouth about King Rick!
It's over.
Stop fighting.
Uh, King Rick?
Many years ago, I was
a soldier in your army.
I was as well.
Oh, me too, my lord.
And proud of it.
What the hell? What's
happening? This is creepy.
I thought they were broken,
but now they're getting up.
Why would all those soldiers bow to Rick?
And the toys, too. What gives?
They're loyal to him.
I don't get it.
I thought everyone here hated King Rick.
Yeah.
There's a structure down here
even King Rick didn't know about.
If you ask me, we should
start searching underground.
I see.
Keep me posted, okay?
Calic.
What are they doing to us now?
Something's jogging me away!
He's gone!
Brother!
Baa-ha-ha-ha!
Hey, hey!
I'm done now!
You can go!
Thou shalt not harm any human.
Thou shalt obey all
orders from the family.
You better follow those rules!
Now go straight through that door!
Keep walking, you'll find a
factory with a port along the way.
March.
Keep quiet and work hard out there.
Okay, little minion.
Those contenders were all pretty tough.
It'll take a long time before they break.
What's happening to me?
I'm trying to stop, but
my body won't listen.
It's like I can't disobey him.
What the hell did you do to me?
What did you turn me into?
She did it!
Hey, get out of the shot, cabbage!
Show us Rebecca!
Wait, why am I watching the
match on this tiny screen?
I'm gonna go cheer for her.
Later, guys! See ya.
Oh, one last thing, though.
When I first got here,
it seemed like everyone in the
country was happy and having fun.
But you guys showed me
how things really are.
What you saw was a surface where winners
are living happy lives, not like us.
Though Flamingo deems the
people who follow him winners.
And anyone who disobeys him losers.
His attitude is no different
than the world government.
The rogues and renegades
are labeled as trash.
And once you sweep them out of sight.
Your country starts looking good.
Well, on the surface at least.
Let's go!
Treasure hunting time!
You know it kind of reminds me
of the country I grew up in,
starts with a bad feeling, then you
start noticing the darker truths.
I got a feeling we've got even uglier
surprises waiting for us out there!
You better keep your guard up, kid.
No problem. I'll see ya!
I can't believe I finally found you!
Many ages ago, our Tantata
ancestors took to the seas.
Not in search of treasure, but in search
of resources that their homeland lacked.
But they could not hide from the big people,
and their encounters never ended well.
Before long, our race was
in danger of going extinct.
Oh, looky, the little people!
When all seemed lost, they came here
to dress Rosa and met with the king.
He offered the tantara a deal.
In exchange for a bit of labor,
he would provide us with a
home, resources, and safety.
And as for the king's
name, it was Don Quixote.
This fateful encounter occurred
more than 900 years ago,
but it's remembered as the beginning
of the darkest age in our history.
We call it the Slave Era.
There are some surviving
manuscripts that detail the
cruelty we faced at the
hands of the royal family.
And they are horrifying.
Our ancestors toiled and toiled
underground, hidden away from the world.
Meanwhile, the big people
above lived a life of luxury.
Built upon the backs of our efforts
with the riches we discovered.
Now, the next hundred years
were part of the blank century?
so the records from that
time are lost to us.
But 800 years ago, a new king
came to power in Dressrosa.
King, we do the prize!
Soon he learned the truth
of our people's sad history,
the centuries of oppression and slavery,
then to our surprise.
With tears streaming down his face,
he bowed his head and offered
us his deepest apologies.
Later, the king devised a plan to help us.
He enacted reparations.
He told us we no longer
needed to slave away.
We could take anything we
required from the country.
And we didn't need to
pay a thing in return.
God!
My bag's missing!
Oh, no!
Someone has stolen my favorite jacket!
All you can do is laugh and let it go!
King Rick declared that our
actions were the work of fairies,
so the citizens accepted
them with good humor.
The legend of the Dressrosa Fairies
was born and continues to this day.
That is so cool!
I love this Rick guy!
Under the rule of the
benevolent Rick dynasty,
a helping hand was always lent to
neighboring countries when they were in need.
Although I can't say that the
kingdom was especially wealthy,
its people were always smiling and
the world thought of them warmly.
Our ancestors paid tribute
to King Rick by planting
flowers and greenery over
the whole countryside.
It was a labor of love
that continued until
the entire kingdom
shimmered like a rainbow.
The Tantara are linked to
the Rick family by a bond
of respect that's been
nourished for over 800 years.
But alas, those many years of
prosperity may be coming to an end.
The Don Quixote family has returned.
Their descendant is king.
Doflamingo cares not
for the Tantata tribe.
He wishes to repeat our tragic history.
First, he sees my daughter, Mon Cherie.
And now that he's taken
500 of our people hostage,
I have no doubt he'd
make slaves of us all.
We won't let him have his way.
We shall be forever free!
And so we fight to oppose that
despot from the Don Quixote
line to defend our fair kingdom
so everyone can live free!
Now we have heroes on our side!
Usalit will bring us victory!
Usalit! Usalit! Usalit!
I'm telling!
You can count on your hero!
Is he awesome or what? Ha ha!
Gingory, you're such a stand-up guy.
I can't believe it.
He's even nice to these little bug people.
What do you do against Robots?
Uh, bugs. In a good way.
Oh, no problem, Bing!
One question? Huh?
Who is that woman fighting
out there in the ring?
The crowd seems to hate her.
But judging by their jeers,
she's related to the former king.
Is there something we don't
know about the Rick dynasty?
There's nothing I don't know!
It happened ten years ago.
King Rick lost the support of his citizens
in a sudden tragedy that struck one night.
He fought for his people until the
end, but that story has been lost.
Riku's entire family can go to hell!
I don't blame them.
The citizens don't know what
really happened that day.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
I failed to protect your mother.
After he took control of the kingdom,
Doflamingo tried to erase
King Riku's bloodline.
But I took Rebecca away and
went into hiding with her.
Thus, she was able to grow into adulthood.
Eventually, we were discovered, and Doflamingo
decided to put her on public display!
I swear,
I will restore the people's faith in King
Rick and I will protect Rebecca from harm,
even if I have to give my life to do it.
That is why we fight to
put an end to this—who
are
you?
you
A failure.
A soldier who couldn't complete his duty.
I let her die.
For as long as I live, I'll never
forget what happened that day.
But Rebecca has forgotten me
because I was turned into a toy.
This toy soldier is brave and true,
in the rain or in the snow
he will stay with you.
She doesn't know.
The truth is I'm Rebecca's father.
Both of you go to hell!
I'll do the same to you!
Watch this—Rebecca's taking advantage
of Logan being distracted and flees.
flees
She's scurrying across
the arena like a rat.
And rolling low, didn't give it a chance.
Blowing down the other contenders
like a field of daisies.
Hey, do you want to see one, Rebecca?
Fight back or die!
But you...
Your grandpa tried to burn us down,
Rebecca, and now he's burning in hell.
She really is King Riku's granddaughter.
If what you say was true, hold it.
What were you before you transformed?
I mean, if you're her father, and
her grandfather is the king...
Everything began on that night.
Answer my question!
Are you a prince or something, huh?
Well, when I think about it,
the signs came before that.
It truly began when a woman named
Monet came to work at the palace.
Oh, her.
That's the bird lady, isn't it?
In only a decade, the whole
kingdom has been transformed.
Its people as well.
Hey, what happened here?
Some pirates were starting a ruckus,
but the royal army ran them out so they
didn't cause much damage in the end.
My gosh, we've gone two weeks
without an inch of rain.
Yeah, still, the flowers never
wilt, even now. Why's that?
It's thanks to the fairies, of course.
No matter how dry it gets, they
always protect the flowers.
I want more! I'm hungry!
If you have strength enough
to shout, you won't starve.
Huh?
No matter how poor we might feel at
times, there's never war here, you know?
And peace is the most important
thing of all, don't you think?
In 800 years of the Rick dynasty, never
once was Dressrosa embroiled in war.
Goodness, that is remarkable.
Yes, almost a miracle.
Until our peace was destroyed by him.
Suddenly he descended upon the palace,
dancing in the darkness like a knight.
Halt! Who's there?
What the hell do you want?
My name is Don Quixote do Flamingo.
I have heard troubling tales of a pirate
named Don Quixote wreaking havoc nearby.
Well, you were right to be troubled.
Though that's only the half of it.
Did you know my ancestors, the Don
Quixote family, once ruled this kingdom?
Even if you've forgotten, I have not.
Thus, I've returned to
take my place as your king!
I know about the havoc you
wreaked by stealing heavenly
tributes before they could
reach the Celestial Dragons,
and how you became a warlord
by blackmailing the government.
What can I say?
Poor saps don't know what to do with me.
You can't threaten someone who's not
afraid of the Celestial Dragons, after all.
Anyway, since you know what I'm
about, let's cut to the chase.
I'll sell you this kingdom
for, say, ten billion berries?
You'd sell me my own kingdom?
As a courtesy.
I could also take it by force if
you don't want to accept my offer!
To avoid bloodshed, I would happily pay?
If I could, that is.
But ten billion berries
is far more than I have.
Is it?
You have until sunrise, so I'd get moving.
You can't get outside help.
This is to test your worth as a king,
and you can't tell your
people about me or our deal.
If you don't like your
odds, then fight me,
but I'll warn you: even if
you win, it won't be pretty.
Your people will be bathed in carnage.
Choose well, your majesty.
The man is a criminal.
A war would be justified, my lord.
Enough fighting to kill is not the answer.
We must never lose sight of
what it means to be human,
but sir, we could never
collect that much money.
Few of our citizens are wealthy,
and no one has nearly that much
besides the Don Quixote family.
Abandoned Dress Rosa, our kingdom
has not engaged in war in 800 years.
That fact is proof of our humanity.
You are not a beast.
We don't kill.
I will not allow it. Listen up.
We have little time.
Split up and lead to different villages.
Collect the 10 billion
from all over the kingdom.
If you can't, the Threlso
will be ruled by pirates.
I fear this won't be pleasant.
We'll
lose the trust of our citizens when we
demand their money, but bear it till morning.
When everything is settled, I will do
everything in my power to make it up to them.
This is the only We can't use
trickery to get out of this.
Every last berry counts—the fate of our
nation is resting on your shoulders!
It's
in the army, it's awfully late!
an emergency.
Listen, I
need you to fight every last berry in
town and bring them here immediately!
immediately Huh?
Whoa, whoa, what's going on?
What do you think the king is
going to say when he hears of this?
We're here on orders from the king.
Hurry!
There's no time left
to explain. Just do it!
Have faith in King Rick!
Don't ask questions and bring the money!
Please, listen to me!
This is too fishy.
It's hopeless.
Who would agree to such
an outlandish request?
The video transponder snail?
People of Dressrosa.
It's King Rick!
He'll settle this mess!
I know this is rather sudden, and it must
seem quite odd, but please hear my plea.
I need to borrow all of your money,
and I need to do so immediately.
It is with great regret that I cannot
offer you a reason for this request.
The king is begging? King Rick?
Why?
This doesn't make sense.
It came out of nowhere, too.
My lord, no.
Raise your head. Stop it.
You have to show some
dignity as our leader.
That's enough.
Stand up.
This is mad.
Think of the history books.
Every descendant of yours will be
ashamed of this crowd's indignity.
Oblating yourself, you'll
turn us into a laughingstock.
King Rick, do you think this is a joke?
I would sacrifice anything for this.
I don't care.
Curse my pride.
I'd chop off my arms and legs, if that's
what it would take to keep my kingdom safe.
Listen, tank.
If things go wrong tonight, I'll
bear the burden and kill Doflamingo.
Surely not.
You can't.
I trust you.
Do your best.
He put his faith, his life, in my hands.
Come on!
What is everyone waiting for?
Let's go get that money! Yeah, guys!
The king's a good man!
If he needs our help that badly,
we don't need to question why.
Yeah, he must have a reason.
Don't worry about it now.
Everyone, bring out your money! No, run!
King Rick, your virtue may save us.
Take it.
Thank you.
I was a fool.
The people of this nation
share the same kindness
the Rick family has shown
them for eight centuries.
This is a wonderful kingdom.
Surely it can be saved!
Thank you!
We need to hurry back to the palace!
Hope this is enough!
Full speed, men!
Captain Tank!
Seems the king went to...
Sivio!
It's on the screen right now!
King Rick!
You didn't have to come
all this way! We got it!
Run away!
King Rick!
I don't know what's happening,
but we're all here to help out.
We trust you completely.
Get away!
King Rick, what's wrong?
Survive!
Stop it!
I'm begging you!
King Rick, please wait!
What are you doing? Go!
Stay away from me, or
I'm going to hurt you!
Soldiers too?
My body is moving on its own!
My lord!
I don't...
understand!
Oh, Rick.
What a naughty king you are.
The knights steal young soldiers.
Don't just stand there gawking.
Why don't you join the dance?
Parasite string!
Now the soldiers are
cutting people down too.
No.
Captain.
Help me.
Why are you doing this, King Rick?
He was such a kind man before.
Is there something
we've done to anger you?
What could I possibly say?
Nothing can justify this.
We're done.
The kingdom is finished.
We fell right into Doflamingo's trap.
The king's lost his mind.
Everyone, run for your lives.
No more, stop.
Hey, hey, can we do it
already, please? Go-fi.
Now, now.
We can't rush things.
I need them trembling with
fear in the depths of despair.
And when this kingdom hates
King Rick with all its heart?
That's when the heroes
can appear! I'm here.